啊
Ah,
现在轮到你了 我活着就是为了告诉你我的秘密
this is when it's come to you really only living so that I can tell my secrets.
我把每一个都画了
I'm painting every single one of them.
每一个大的
Every bigger.
你永远不会吃东西
You would never never eat.
是的
Yeah.
威胁是什么
The threat of what that is that,
像河
like river,
你有很多东西要学
you have a lot to learn.
你叫什么名字
What's your name,
玛格丽特
Margaret?
你不会想办法和他在那里的亲密关系调情吗
Wouldn't you manage to flirt with his close down there?
你知道的
You know,
我喜欢你
I like you.
好吧
Well,
这一切都在发生
this is all happening.
强大的克莱尔
Mighty Clair,
社区拯救儿童
community for saving the child's,
沃尔特是上帝的赐福
Walter is a blessing.
他不喜欢这些东西
He didn't love the stuff.
通过他们的眼睛
By their eyes.
眼睛是心灵的窗户
The eyes are the windows of the soul.
这就是为什么油漆有这么大
That's why the paint have so big.
我一直都是这么做的
I've always done it that way.
可悲的是
Sadly,
人们不买女人或画
people don't buy lady or the painting,
说计划
says scheme.
我强烈的飓风
I'm keen hurricane.
今天的微笑已经售罄
The smile was sold out today has over you.
大眼睛
big eyes,
源的绘画
the source paintings,
他看到了胰脏的图片
and he saw the pictures of the pancreas.
他说诗歌学校的明信片
and he says postcards of pictures of poetic school.
这是一个运动
It's a movement.
现在
Now.
你是掷硬币还是诚实地掷
Are you flip it Throw them honestly,
我不敢相信我在这里
I can't believe I'm here.
然而
However,
很多事情让你困惑
a lot of things that you confused,
我付出了代价 我想我的孩子不知道你是什么样的人
I paid it that what is troubling you I'd like to my child doesn't know what kind of person is.
你丈夫有一个人是我生命的一部分
Your husband had got a person who was a part of my being.
签署的细胞
Signing the cells,
这听起来有点令人困惑
it sounds a bit confusing,
不是吗
doesn't it?
王指的就是我
King means me.
如果你告诉任何人这个帝国崩溃了
If you tell anyone this empire collapses,
你可以抑制
you can suppress.
第二个来自一个遥远的团队
The second arrived from a distant team.
看起来像绘画
Look like paintings,
这类
that class.
它不是我的火焰
It is not my flame,
我说
I said.
周五
On Friday.